http://www.inetco.com/privacy/

Regulatory Compliance
ATM Cash-Out Attacks, Man-In-The-Middle Attacks and Transaction Reversal Fraud
Resources
What is Transaction Data?
Request a Demo
Request a demonstration to see INETCO products in action.
Regulatory Compliance
ATM Cash-Out Attacks, Man-In-The-Middle Attacks and Transaction Reversal Fraud
Resources
What is Transaction Data?
INETCO’s Privacy Policy & Terms of Use
Customer privacy is important to INETCO. We strive to keep your personal information confidential. This statement of privacy explains data collection and use in situations where we request information about you. Please take a moment to read the INETCO privacy policy to learn how we handle your personal information.
Contact information
If you have any questions, INETCO’s head office is located at the following address:
Suite 295 – 4664 Lougheed Highway
Burnaby BC, V5C 5T5
We can be reached via e-mail at marketing@inetco.com, or you can reach us by telephone at 604.451.1567.
Why we collect personal information
INETCO collects and uses your personal information to improve the content of our Web site, to offer you superior customer service, to provide you with convenient access to our products and services, and to make a wider range of services available to you.
In addition, we use your personal information to keep you up to date on the latest product announcements, software updates, special offers, and other information we think you’d like to hear about. This may occasionally include information from other technology companies about products and services that can add value to your INETCO products. From time to time, we may also use your personal information to contact you to participate in a market research survey, so that we can gauge customer satisfaction and develop better products.
Protecting your privacy rights
In protecting your privacy rights, INETCO Systems Limited:
Safeguards customers’ information from unauthorized access.
Honors consumers’ requests to remove their names from our telephone, e-mail, mail solicitation lists, or database. If you wish to remove your personal data from our database, please let us know by sending an email with the subject line, “Delete” to marketing@inetco.com.
Strives to keep customer records current and accurate.
Collects, maintains and uses customer information that is necessary to provide the most helpful and personalized products and services to meet consumers’ needs.
Maintains the full confidentiality of customer information when undertaking projects with third party companies.
Honors requests from customers for account information the company has about them.
How we collect personal information
We may collect information about you in several ways. For example, we might ask you to volunteer your contact information when you correspond with us via e-mail, call us to make a purchase or request service, register to attend a webinar or download a whitepaper, or participate in an online survey.
For each visitor to our Web pages, we collect the domain names and the aggregate information on what pages you access or visit.  In addition, when you register a new INETCO product, sign up for INETCO support services, opt-in or ask to be included in an email mailing list, we collect and store the information you provide (name, address, company, job title, telephone number, email) in a secure database.
With respect to cookies: We use cookies to ensure that visitors do not have to fill in the same web form more than once to access the information of interest to you. These cookies also enable us to track and target the interests of our visitors to enhance the experience on our website.
With respect to Ad Servers: We do not partner with or have special relationships with any ad server companies.
In some of our emails to you, we use a “click-through URL.” When you click one of these URLs, you pass through a web server before arriving at the website that is your destination. We track click-throughs to help us determine your interest in particular topics and measure the effectiveness of our customer communications.
When we disclose personal information
INETCO may occasionally share your personal contact information with carefully selected technology companies to keep you informed about related products and services. This is typically done in aggregate form. For example, when new software is released, we may work with our channel and reseller partners to ensure that you’re aware of the latest INETCO software available.
If you do not want to receive promotional information from INETCO or these technology companies, request that your name be taken off the mailing list by emailing marketing@inetco.com.
At times we may be required by law or legal process to disclose your personal information. We may also disclose information about you if we believe that disclosure is necessary for the public interest.
If you supply us with your postal address, you may receive periodic mailings from us with information on new products and services or upcoming events. If you do not wish to receive such mailings, please let us know by sending an email marketing@inetco.com.
Persons who supply us with their telephone numbers may receive telephone contact from us with information regarding new products and services or upcoming events. If you do not wish to receive such telephone calls, please let us know by sending an email to marketing@inetco.com.
How we protect your personal information
INETCO safeguards the security of the data you send us with physical, electronic, and managerial procedures.  We have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our site.
Access to your personal information
If you would like to review or correct any personal information that INETCO may have about you, email us at marketing@inetco.com.
Our companywide commitment to privacy
To ensure that your personal information remains confidential, we communicate these privacy guidelines to every INETCO employee.
INETCO does not knowingly solicit personal information from children or send them requests for personal information.
From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If we are going to use your personal information differently from that stated at the time of collection, we will try to contact you via email using the most recent information we have. If you have not given us permission to communicate with you, you will not be contacted, nor will we use your personal information in a new manner.
The INETCO Customer Privacy Policy is subject to change at any time. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our Web site. We encourage you to review the privacy policy regularly for any changes.
If you have questions, or feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us at the above addresses, phone number or email: marketing@inetco.com.
Last updated:  May 17, 2018
GET A DEMO
1 MIN VIDEO
CONTACT US
ProductsINETCO Insight
INETCO Insight Data Access Options
INETCO Analytics
Professional Services
sales@inetco.com
Sign up to receive INETCO updates:
Sign Up Now!
© 2006-2020 INETCO Systems Ltd.
All Rights Reserved.
All trademarks, registered trademarks, trade names, service marks and logos referenced herein are owned or used under license by INETCO Systems Limited.
Sitemap Privacy Policy
